Guide to the Multicultural Student Services Center records, 1969-2016 RG0056
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Multicultural Student Services Center, 1969-1993; 1980-1993; RG0056 Series 1
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Monthly Report, June 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Implementation of the Available Funds File (AFI) for Validation Purposes, April 8, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Project Enrich/ College Knowledge Precollege Seminar, July 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Faculty/ Employee Assistance Program Memorandum, April 8, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Activities for Fiscal Year 1987-88, July 18, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Proposal for Annual Martin Luther King, Jr. Awards, April 4, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Change of Sports Sponsorship: Letter to the Hatchet, March 20, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Naming the Minority Student Services Center Correspondence, April 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Taxation of Graduate Level Tuition Benefits, August 18, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - General Correspondence to and from Valerie L. Epps, 1988-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Diversity Program Clearinghouse, 1991-1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Diversity clearing house, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Valerie L. Epps Correspondence [1/5], 1973-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Valerie L. Epps Correspondence [2/5], 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Valerie L. Epps Correspondence [3/5], 1989-1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Valerie L. Epps Correspondence [4/5], 1989-1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Valerie L. Epps Correspondence [5/5], 1989-1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Directory of Volunteer Opportunities for Youth, June 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - MLK, Jr. Convocation Committee, 1989-1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Director of Lisner Auditorium Candidates, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Valerie L. Epps Day [1/2], March 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Valerie L. Epps Day [2/2], March 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Various MSSC Program Information and Promotional Material, 1990-1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Commitment to the Abolition of Apartheid in South Africa, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - A Model Questionnaire for Campus Self-Assessments, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - A Letter to New Students, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - College Work-Study Program Materials, 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Student Financial Aid Processing, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Opening Convocation: Celebrating a New Year, a New President, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Students SAT Scores, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Washington, D.C. Association of Urban Bankers, Inc. (WAUB) 1989 Annual Awards Banquet, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - WordPerfect Student Workbook Promotional Materials, March 7, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Supply Order, May 2, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Request to Reserve Facilities and Services in the Marvin Center Form, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Graduating Senior Survey: Summary of Comparison between Minority and White Students, 1988, April 4, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Summer Scholar Program: Resident Assistant Position, June - July 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Undergraduate Applicant List, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Report: New Applicants Eligible for Financial Aid, June - July 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Office Hours Schedule Forms (Blank), Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) at The George Washington University: A Report on the First Five Years, 1969-1974; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Updated Supplement of the Five-Year Report, 1969-1976; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Updated Supplement of the First Five-Year Report, 1975-1977; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Updated Supplement of the First Five-Year Report, 1975-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Recommendation Letters, 1969-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Student Admissions Representative (STAR): The Basic Campus Tour, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - University of the District of Columbia, University College: Learning Survival Package, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Washington D.C. Area High Schools, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Creating Group Climate in the Learning Experience, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Peer Counseling, 1976-1979; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Plans and Objectives, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Quick Reference Guide to Academic Procedures at The George Washington University, 1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Academic Monitoring System, March 30, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Handbook for the Educational Opportunity Program (EOP), November 1977; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Fall 1988 HI/SCIP Students, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - HI/SCIP Applicants Fall 1989, 1988-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - List of Spring 1989 HI/SCIP Students, February 13, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Pre-college Review and Enrichment Program (PREP), 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Pre-college Review and Enrichment Program (PREP), 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Fall 1988 Tutorial Program Report, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Newsletter, 1985-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Test Taking Techniques, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Student Handbook of General Academic Procedures at GWU, compiled by EOP Peer Counselors, Fall 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Barbara S. Framer's Resume, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Ahuruezenma Anyatonwu's Part-time Employee Time Sheet, May 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    Ahuruezenma Anyatonwu was an office/lab assistant.
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Pre-college Review and Enrichment Program (PREP) Orientation Sessions, 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Pre-college Review and Enrichment Program (PREP) Summer Session Registration, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Pre-college Review and Enrichment Program (PREP) Syllabus, 1988-1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Original Copies of Pre-college Program (EOP) Materials for Duplication, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    The materials within the folder are: 1) Math Test; 2) Grammar Pre-test; 3) Third Session Courses; and 4) PREP Schedule Form.
  - Summer Pre-college Review and Enrichment Program (PREP) Seminar, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - I Have a Dream Foundation Pre-college Programs, 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Spend an Afternoon with a College Student Registration Form, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Reading Laboratory Report, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Pre-college Review and Enrichment Program (PREP) Students Who Have Committed Lists, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - The George Washington University Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Pre-college Review and Enrichment (PREP) Program Report, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Audit Request: Time Sheets, July 25, 1994; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - The George Washington University Federal Work-Study Program Weekly Hours Reports, 1993-1994; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    Folder includes Social Security Numbers.
  - The George Washington University MSSC Time Sheets, 1993; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Valerie L. Epps's Travel File, 1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    File includes Social Security Numbers.
  - Curley, Tynicka (Fall 1989 admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Restricted access due to the presence of social security numbers, grades, and SAT scores.
  - Cole, Lawrencia, Summer 1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Cole, Portia, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Colon-Francia, Angelita, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cooper, Jacqueline, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cooper, Keya, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Conti, Christina Maria, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Cramer, James, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Crocker, Siontelle, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Crosby, Anthony, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Carter, Sonja, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chichester, Naya, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Cha-Champ, Charmaine, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Chan, Kim, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Chase, Hawanya (Fall 1989 admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Chin Jr., Michael R., 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Chin, Pedro (Fall 1989 admit), 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Chu, Jack, 1986-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 175th Anniversary Working Committee Responsibilities and Working Agendas, 1993; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Chichester, Mark [1/3], 1987-1993; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Chichester, Mark [2/3], 1986-1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Chichester, Mark [3/3], 1988-1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Davis, Wilnetta, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Dean, Sheri, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - De Guzman, Edgar Allen, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - De Guzman, Rosemarie, 1990-1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Dixon, Angela, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Dockery, Matthew (Transfer), 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Dobson, Dama, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Donaldson, Tony, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Dopkin, Edward, June 21, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Dorsey, Angela, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Davis, Diane (Transfer), 1983-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Davis, Leonard, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Davis, Michael, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Eason, Brenda (Fall 1989 Admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Edwards, Anthony, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Edwards, Peggy, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Egwim, Kelechi (Fall 1989 Admit), 1989-1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Encinas, Mary, 1982-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Evans, Althea, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Felix, Sherry, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Ferrette, Chelsea, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Fletcher, Diedra (Fall 1989 admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Ford, Tarita, 1987-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Foster, Nicole (Fall 1989 admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Freeman, Reba, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Gadson, Rhayne, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Gaines, Danee, 1987-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Gallego, Anafabiola, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Gambrill, Ernest, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Garibay, Angela, 1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Garrett, Mamye (Transfer), 1982-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Garland, Sonja, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Gibson, Terrica, March 9, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Glennon, Robyn, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Gordon, Keenan, March 29, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Graves, Monica (PREP 89-90), May 30, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Gray, Yvonne, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Green, Candace, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Griffith, Marcia, February 15, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Guerrier, Sophia, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Hill, Prinsea, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Holmes, Tina, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Horner, Brenda (Transfer), 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Howard, Willie (Fall 1989 admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Huang, Guo, 1985-1989 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Huang, Ruo Gu, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Hughes, Ronald, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Haines, Kali (Fall 1989 admit), 1989-1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Hartridge, Tanya, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Hassan, Aisha, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Harris, Timothy (Waived PREP), 1983-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Hawthorne, Pamela, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Henderson, Lorita, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Hester, Garry, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Hill, Anita, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Hill, Betsy, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Hill, Ian, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Hall, Andrea, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Hall, Morse, April 6, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Harley, Arneida (Transfer), 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Harvey, Dwayne, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Ihediohanma, Clothida, 1990-1993; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Ibe, Oluchi (Fall 1989 admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Jenkins, Orlando, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Jarrett, Erica (Fall 1989 admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Jenkins, Yvette, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Johnson, Harvey, 1988-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Johnson, Ivan, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Johnson, Kendra, 1987-1989; RG0056 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Johnson, Maureen, 1985-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Jones, Carole, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Jones, Cortella (Fall 1989 admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Jones, Crystal, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Jones, Mikki, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Jackson, April, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Jackson, Kevin, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Jackson, Matthew, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Jackson, Tina, 1985-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Johnson, Jeanett, 1993; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Kamara, Ismatu, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Kemp, Karyn, 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Kendall, Lyzelle, 1986-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Key, Renee (Transfer), 1986-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Kidane, Kiflay, 1986-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Kipple, Nicole (Transfer), 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Lai, Kar-Yuk, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Lone, Mario, 1986-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Lucas, Rose, 1985-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Luong, Duo, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Lyon, Nicolle, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Little, Marcus, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Little, Stacy (Fall 1989 admit), RG0056 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Littlejohn, Valerie, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Mun, Lin, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Lodeon, Jeremy (Fall 1989 admit) (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Lodeon, Samuel, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Logan, Angela (Fall 1989 admit) (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Klebau, Brenda, 1986-1989 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Kok, Nancy (Fall 1989 admit), 1989-04-26 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Lee, Gee, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Lee, Chung, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Lee, Donna, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Lam, Warren (Admit 1989) (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Lee. Fannie, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Lee, Geraldine Marie, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Lee, Kit, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Lee, Nelson, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Lee, Sherree (PREP 89-90), 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Lewis, Erika, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Adams, Annette, 1980-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, Gwyn, 1980-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Blackmon, Carol, 1980-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Boddie, Jeffrey, 1980-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Bradshaw, Rebecca, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bruce, Laverne, 1980-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Christiano, Timothy, 1980-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Jefferson, Cameron, 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Jew, Linda, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Paula, 1980-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Jones, Angela, 1980-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - King, Bibiana, 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Lee, Chin, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Longshore, Derek, 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Parker, Patricia Ann, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Pervall, Gina, 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Petty, Bennett, 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Proctor, Rae Ann, 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Simons, Wilma, 1980-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Williamson, Rohan, 1980-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Zephirin, Marguerite, 1980-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - List of HI/SCIP Student, 1983-1984, 1982-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Bretzfelder, Marc, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Bell, Fontella, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Dooling, Daniella, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Drayne, Katherine, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Guishard, Karen, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Jackson, Toni, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Kalas, Justine L., 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Lee, Ka, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Leo, Leonard, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Maiden, Tonya, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Mays, Rachel, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Nesmith, Rhonda, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Mierzwa, Robyn, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Mooers, Sarah, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Root, Victoria, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Shrader, Karen, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Topps, Andrea, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Temple, John, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Uy, Euler, 1983-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Vickerie, Sharen, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Vy, Leim, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Wood, Margaret, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Woolfork, Stacey, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Bennett, Karl, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Bertannt, Nanette, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Blust, Christina, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Chesley, Anthony, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Coleva, Eleni, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Fedoruk, Tanya, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Flack, Hillary, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Fothergill, Alice, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Hodges, Laura, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Hudgens, David, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Hyslop, Alison, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Lee, George, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Lesser, Rick, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Mason, Kerwin, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Mendelsohn, Martin, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Mierzwa, Peter, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Nolan, Virgina, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Phua, John, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Risser, David, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Schandelmeir, Julia, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Stearns, Susan, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Sung, Mark, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Washington, Anne, 1982-193; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Phua, John, 1982 May 13; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Nolan, Virgina, 1983 March- May; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Mason, Kerwin, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Lee, George, 1983 May 07; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Brown, Phyllis, 1981-1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Evans, Thomas, 1981-1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Moy, Chun, 1981-1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Stubbs, John, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Williams, Pamela, 1981-1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Apparent HI/SCIP Denials, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Carr, Molly, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Cohen, Jeremiah, 1984 August; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Fleisig, Alexis, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Fletcher, Carl, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Hickman, Tonia, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Howell, Leah, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Jones, Kelly, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Kalish, Seth, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Karimah, Donnell, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Karlen, Caroline, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Kelly, Paula, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Firshner, Melody, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Knauff, Margareta, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Lambert, Sage, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Levin, James, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - McDiarmid, Jennifer, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Nealson, Caroline, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - O'Hara, Robert, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Quander II, Joseph, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Quinn, Granthan, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Righini, John, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Seralie, Alan, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Sharkey, Anne, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Taylor, Dennis, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 102)